Works Progress Administration (WPA) Phonodisc Collection
Works Progress Administration (WPA) Phonodisc Collection
- 1939 season
  - Program No. 55 Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1939; wpa_phono_223; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    March, from Le coq d'or; Dance d'esclaves, from Les Troyens ballet; WPA spot; Waltz, from Swan Lake suite
  - Program No. 56 [Forum] String Quartette, 1939; wpa_phono_224; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    First movement from the Quartet in C minor, Opus 18, No. 4: allegro, ma non tanto; Col. Francis C. Harrington on the WPA; Molly on the Shore, Irish reel. Individual players uncredited.
  - Program No. 57 Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1939; wpa_phono_225; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Ruy Blas, Op. 95; speech by John M. Carmody, Administrator Federal Works Agency; Fandango, Op. 51 No. 2.
  - Program No. 58 Madrigal Singers, 1939; wpa_phono_226; folk songs, including some Christmas; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Patapan, French Christmas carol sung in English; The Dark-eyed Sailor; The Springtime of the Year; Talk on the WPA and European War by Howard O. Hunter, Deputy WPA commissioner; Whither Runneth My Sweetheart, tenor/soprano, piano accompaniment; The Turtle Dove (The Wassail Song).
  - Program No. 59 Civic Orchestra, 1939; wpa_phono_227; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Slavonic Dance in E minor; Talk by Corrington Gill, Assistant Commissioner of WPA; Adagio, from Symphony No. 2, incomplete performance.
  - Program No. 60 Concert Band, 1939; wpa_phono_228; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Caliph of Baghdad; Talk on WPA Engineering by Major Bartley M. Harloe, Assistant Commissioner; Treasure Waltz from The Gypsy Baron.
  - Program No. 61 Federal Symphony, 1939; wpa_phono_229; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Egmont; Talk on Women in the WPA by Florence S. Kerr, Assistant Commissioner; The Dance.
  - Program No. 62 Federal Symphony, 1939; wpa_phono_230; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00 (Oversize 1)
    Overture to Der Freischütz; Talk by Colonel H. W. Clark, Commissioner of of the Public Works Administration; Waltz, from Sleeping Beauty.
- 1940 season
  - Program No. 1 Mass. [Massachusetts] WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_231; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Secret of Suzanne; Talk by Edward Bruce, Chief of Fine Arts Sectional (dubbed); Island Sketches - Vision of Capri.
  - Program No. 2 WPA Madrigal Singers of Boston, 1940; wpa_phono_232; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Alleluia! Today is Christ Risen; Matona, Mia Cara; Mon coeur se recommande A Vous (My heart commends itself to thee); Talk by W. E. Reynolds, Commissioner of Public buildings; La Pastorella (What shall we give the little shepherdess); Come Away Sweet Love and Play Thee.
  - Program No. 3 Mass. [Massachusetts] WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_233; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Selections of 2nd and 4th movements from Concerti Grossi for String, Op. 1; Talk by Nathan Straus, Administrator United States Housing Authority; Scherzo from 3rd movement from Symphony No. 4.
  - Program No. 4 WPA Madrigal Singers of Boston, 1940; wpa_phono_234; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    In mirth and in gladness; In these delightful pleasant groves; Talk by Thomas H. McDonald, Commissioner Public Roads administrator (dubbed); Spring is here again, sung in French; Sweet Nymphs that trip Along.
  - Program No. 5 Mass. [Massachusetts] WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_235; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Rêverie, from Suite Bergamasque; Talk by Mayor Harold H. Burton of Cleveland (dubbed); Island Sketches - Sicilian Autumn.
  - Program No. 6 WPA Madrigal Singers of Boston, 1940; wpa_phono_236; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Cantate Domino; Die Beredsamkeit (drinking song "Eloquence"); Talk by Florence Kerr, Assistant Commissioner; Sweet Honey Sucking Bees.
  - Program No. 7 Mass. [Massachusetts] WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_237; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Introduction to Golden Cockerel; Talk by Colonel Francis C. Harrington, Commissioner; Polonaise from Christmas Eve suite.
  - Program No. 8 WPA Southland Singers of Boston, 1940; wpa_phono_238; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Poor Mourner got Home at Last; Sometimes I Feel Like a Motherless Child; Talk by Major Bartley M. Harloe, Assistant Commissioner; My Lord what a Morning.
  - Program No. 9 Mass. [Massachusetts] WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_239; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from the ballet Le Cid; Talk by Dr. Paul de Kruif, Author; Pomp and Circumstance March No. 1 in D Major with organ.
  - Program No. 10 WPA Madrigal Singers of Boston, 1940; wpa_phono_240; psalms, sacred music, folk songs; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Praise God in His Holy Temple, 150th Psalm (En son temple), sung in French; Oh Great Mystery (O Magnum Misterium), sung in French; Talk by Corrington Gill, Assistant Commissioner; If I Must Die I Will Die of Love, sung in French; Fair Phyllis I Saw Sitting All Along, sung in English.
  - Program No. 11 Mass. [Massachusetts] WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_241; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Suite in B minor: Rondeau; Bouree; Badinerie; Talk by Howard O. Hunter, Deputy Commissioner; The Bridal Procession from Le coq d'or.
  - Program No. 12 WPA Southland Singers of Boston, 1940; wpa_phono_242; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Were you There?; Satisfied with Jesus, Gospel Hymn; Talk by Florence Kerr, Assistant Commissioner, on Women in the WPA - Arts; Too Late; Sit Down, Servant, folk song.
  - Program No. 13 Southern California Colored Choir 85 Voices, 1940; wpa_phono_243; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Lift Every Voice and Sing, piano accompaniment; I Feel Like a Motherless Child; Armor of God, Edward Jones composer [?]; It's All Over Me, piano accompaniment; WPA spot - U. S. Public Health Service; Excerpts from The Messiah: Surely He Hath Borne Our Griefs, piano accompaniment; Hallelujah Chorus, piano accompaniment.
  - Program No. 14 Southern California Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_244; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Libusa; Talk by Dr. Thomas Parran Jr., Surgeon General of the United States on Public Health Service; Legend, from Opus 59.
  - Program No. 15 Southern California Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_245; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Opening of Act III of Tristan and Isolde; Talk by C. R. Smith, President of the American Airlines, on WPA Airport Construction; Polonaise from Eugen Onegin.
  - Program No. 16 Southern California Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_246; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Young prince and princess from Scheherazade; Talk by H. W. Cameron, Director of the National Safety Council; Overture to Prometheus, Op. 43.
  - Program No. 17 Southern California Light Opera Orchestra and Chorus, 1940; wpa_phono_247; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from The Merry Widow: Villia; The Women; Talk by Wallace Beery, famous screen star, on the WPA projects; I love you so (Merry Widow Waltz); Sonya and Prince Danilo Story and Song.
  - Program No. 18 Southern California Light Opera Orchestra and Chorus, 1940; wpa_phono_248; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from The Chocolate Soldier, sung in English: Bulgarian Chorus - Seek the Spy; My Hero; Talk by Dr. Paul de Kruif, noted author; Falling in Love; Finaletto to Act 2.
  - Program No. 19 Southern California Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_249; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Idyll, tone poem; Talk by H. W. Cameron, Director of the National Safety Council on Traffic Safety; Cortege, from Petite Suite.
  - Program No. 20 Southern California Colored Choir, 1940; wpa_phono_250; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Dark Water, a capella; Little David Play on Your Harp, soloists with chorus, a capella; Heaven is a Beautiful Place; WPA spot - Incapacitated Mothers; Goodbye Africa, soloists with chorus; I'm Newborn Again.
  - Program No. 21 New York Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_251; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Rêverie du soir (Evening Reverie) from Suite algérienne; Talk by Honorable John M. Carmody, Administrator Federal Works Agency; Fête Bohème from Scènes pittoresques.
  - Program No. 22 Southern California Colored Choir, 1940; wpa_phono_252; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    85 Voices Choir. Poor Mourner's Got a Home At Last, soloist with chorus, a capella; Four and Twenty Elders, soloist with male chorus; Down by the River, from movie "Mississippi", soloists with chorus; WPA spot; One Morning Soon, male chorus; Great Day, full chorus, piano accompaniment.
  - Program No. 23 Southern California Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_253; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Tango, premiere performance; Talk by Dr. Paul de Kruif, noted authority on medical subjects; Overture, from David, premiere performance. California composers.
  - Program No. 24 Southern California Light Opera Orchestra and Chorus, 1940; wpa_phono_254; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from "The Vagabond King": My Dear Mother; Only a Rose, duet reprise; Talk by Wallace Beery, famous screen star; Act 2 Finale: Some Day, ensemble and soloist; Song of the Vagabonds, soloist and male ensemble.
  - Program No. 25 Southern California Mexican Sypica Orchestra [sic], 1940; wpa_phono_255; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Mi chiquito, orchestra; No niegues (Don't Deny That Once You Loved Me Truly), female vocalist with orchestra; Mi Morena, male vocalist with orchestra; WPA spot; Little Jesusita, march.
  - Program No. 26 Southern California Colored Choir, 1940; wpa_phono_256; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Steal Away, female soloist with chorus, a capella; Every Time I Feel the Spirit, female soloist with chorus, a capella; You May Bury Me In the East, female soloist with chorus, a capella; WPA spot re: Roads; That Great Gettin' up Morning, soloist with chorus, a capella; O, Southland!, soloists with chorus, piano accompaniment.
  - Program No. 27 Northern California Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_257; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Andante to the Clock symphony; WPA spot re: Roads; Allelujah, from Exsultate Jubilate, soloist with orchestra
  - Program No. 28 Northern California Symphony Orchestra, 1940; wpa_phono_258; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Menuetto, from the Clock symphony; WPA spot re: Employment Flexibility; Voices of Spring
  - Program No. 29 Southern California Symphony Orchestra and Grand Opera Chorus, 1940; wpa_phono_259; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00 (Oversize 1)
    Soloists, chorus, and orchestra. Excerpts from Hänsel und Gretel: Part 1 from Opening of Act 2; Talk by C. R. Smith, president of the American Airlines on the WPA and Airports; Part 2, Finale of Act 2.
  - Program No. 30 New Jersey WPA Opera Company, 1940; wpa_phono_260; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Bell Chorus from "Pagliacci"; Pilgrim's Song; Talk by James L. Feiser, Vice Chairman in charge of Domestic Operations of the American Red Cross, on WPA in Emergencies; Great is Jehovah, sung in English by soloist with chorus, orchestra.
  - Program No. 31 New York City Symphony, 1940; wpa_phono_261; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Selections from The Seasons Ballet 4th picture - Winter: Introduction; Frost; Talk by Fiorello LaGuardia, Mayor of New York City; Ice; Hail; Snow.
  - Program No. 32 New Jersey WPA Opera Company, 1940; wpa_phono_262; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Cigarette Chorus from Carmen, sung in French; Clarions of War, from Il Trovatore, sung in Italian; Talk by Senator Robert M. La Follette, Jr.; Grand Finale from The Gondoliers.
  - Program No. 33 New York City Symphony, 1940; wpa_phono_263; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Marche Miniature from Suite No. 1; Berceuse, from Suite No. 2 Caucasian Sketches; Talk by Honorable Thomas Vernor Smith, Congressman at large from Illinois [retired SU professor]; March (Georgian March) from Suite No. 2 Caucasian Sketches.
- 1941 season
  - Program No. 1 New York City Symphony, 1941; wpa_phono_264; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Souvenir de Florence. Adagio Cantabile, first section; Talk by Honorable Thomas Vernor Smith, Congressman at large from Illinois [retired Syracuse University professor]; Adagio Cantabile, 2nd section e conmoto D major. Arranged for strings orchestra.
  - Program No. 2 Northern California Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_265; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Spanish Caprice: Variations and Alborada; WPA spot; Gypsy scene and Alborada; Fandango
  - Program No. 3 New York City Symphony, 1941; wpa_phono_266; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Andante for strings No. 3, Op. 17; Talk by James L. Feiser, Vice Chairman in Charge of Domestic Operations for the American Red Cross on WPA in disaster relief (emergency); Hopak from Sorochintsy Fair (Little Russian dance).
  - Program No. 4 United States Marine Band, 1941; wpa_phono_267; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Thomas Jefferson March; WPA spot in National Defense; American Patrol March; Hail America March.
  - Program No. 5 United States Navy Band, 1941; wpa_phono_268; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Stars and Stripes Forever March; Navy Blue March; WPA spot: National Defense, Navy; Hail to the Spirit of Liberty
  - Program No. 6 United States Marine Band, 1941; wpa_phono_269; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Festival March; WPA spot: "We'll Prepare America" National Defense Spot; Semper Fidelis March
  - Program No. 7 United States Navy Band, 1941; wpa_phono_270; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    All Hands March; Liberty Bell March; WPA spot/Navy constructions - national defense; Navy Patrol March
  - Program No. 8 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_271; patriotic music; Vinyl record; running time 15:00
    Official West Point March; Man of the Hour; WPA spot: Army/Air Corps/ WPA developments; Boys of the Old Brigade; King Cotton
  - Program No. 9 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_272; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Invincible Eagle; Americans All; WPA spot - Defense against aggressor with WPA improvements; Law and Order March; Adoration, based on a theme from "America the Beautiful".
  - Program No. 10 United States Navy Band, 1941; wpa_phono_273; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Stars and Stripes Forever March; Nave Blue March; WPA spot: "We're preparing America"; Hail to the Spirit of Liberty March. Short program with either the music or voice tracks dubbed (mixed down or edited together) in.
  - Program No. 11 United States Navy Band, 1941; wpa_phono_274; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Bolero; Moonlove; WPA spot: 2nd Line of Defense; Josephine. Assembled (edited together) program.
  - Program No. 12 United States Navy Band, 1941; wpa_phono_275; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Father of Victory March; Woodpecker's Song; WPA spot - preparedness program; Moonlight Serenade; Pasadena Day March. Arranged (edited together) program.
  - Program No. 13 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_276; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Official West Point March; Boys of the Old Brigade March; Talk by General George C. Marshall, Chief of Staff, U. S. Army; Adoration, based on a theme of "America the Beautiful"; Up the Street March.
  - Program No. 14 WPA Opera Company, 1941; wpa_phono_277; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    New Jersey Opera Company: Bell Chorus, from Pagliacci, chorus with orchestra; Pilgrim's Song, chorus with orchestra; Talk by Jay Franklin, writer, radio commentator and newspaper columnist on important WPA benefits; Great is Jehovah, soloists, chorus with orchestra.
  - Program No. 15 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_278; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Pierrot; American Army March; Talk by Howard O. Hunter, deputy commissioner, WPA, on legal resolutions and laws to protect WPA workers and voting; Three Solitaires (A trio of trumpets). Edited (mixed) program, audio not up to standard.
  - Program No. 16 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_279; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Field Artillery March, men's chorus; Official West Point March; WPA spot - defense work in wartime, "Newspaper Headlines" with sound effects and more elaborate production values; Boys of the Old Brigade March. Edited (mixed) program.
  - Program No. 17 United States Navy Band, 1941; wpa_phono_280; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Gate City; Pasadena Day; Talk by Donald M. Nelson, Coordinator of National Defense Purchases; Glory of the Trumpets March; National Emblem. Edited (mixed) program.
  - Program No. 18 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_281; patriotic music; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    National Defense March; Soldiers on Parade March; Talk by Dr. Thomas Parran, Jr., Surgeon General of the United States on health protection measures; Riders for the Flag March. Edited (mixed) program.
  - Program No. 19 United States Navy Band, 1941; wpa_phono_282; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    National Emblem March; Moonlight Serenade; Talk by Stuart Chase, author, CPA on government book keeping/ WPA; Glory of the Trumpets. Edited (mixed) program.
  - Program No. 20 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_283; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Our Bugler March; Hail America; Talk by Ida Bailey Allen on the health of children, school lunch program; The Pilgrim Concert March.
  - Program No. 21 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_284; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Purple Pageant March; Cripple Creek, descriptive melody; Talk by Henry Dennison of Dennison Manufacturing Co. on the WPA; Riders for the Flag March.
  - Program No. 22 New York City Symphonic Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_285; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    New York City Symphonic Band (label is wrong). The Arkansas Traveler; Talk by Melvyn Douglas on the WPA and defense; Excerpts from Pictures at an Exhibition: The Hut of Baba-Yaga; The Great Gates of Kiev.
  - Program No. 22A United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_286; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    National Defense March; Squads Right March; Interview of Pvt. John Edward Lawton, first selectee to be inducted under the Selective Service Act on Nov. 18, 1940 by Captain Charles G. Duffy, interviewer at Fort Devens, Massachusetts; Knightsbridge March.
  - Program No. 23 United States Army Band, 1941; wpa_phono_287; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Hail America March; Senn Triumphal, march; Talk by Earl G. Harrison, U. S. Director of Alien Registration on how the WPA is assisting in the alien registration program; American Army March.
  - Program No. 24 Special Christmas Program: Mass. [Massachusetts] WPA Symphony Orchestra and Singers, 1941; wpa_phono_288; Christmas concert; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Concert from Brattle Hall, Cambridge, MA. A Dream of Christmas, orchestra; Talk by Robert E. Sherwood, playwright and author; Pastoral Symphony, from Messiah, orchestra; O Come, All Ye Faithful (Adeste Fideles), chorus, a capella.
  - Program No. 25 New York City Symphonic Band, 1941; wpa_phono_289; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Russian Dance from Swan Lake ballet; Talk by Dr. Frank Kingdon, Clergyman, College President, author, humanitarian on the WPA; Overture to Don Juan. Includes correspondence: 2 WPA letters regarding press release.
  - Program No. 26 New York City Symphonic Band, 1941; wpa_phono_290; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Waltz from The Queen of Sheba; Talk by Emily Newell Blair, author, Women in the national defense, WPA activities; Dance of the Comedians from The Bartered Bride. Includes correspondence: 2 WPA letters regarding press release for radio announcers.
  - Program No. 27 Massachusetts WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_291; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Fingal's Cave, from The Hebrides; Talk by Rex Stout, author and lecturer, on the WPA in the community; Esplanade Waltz by Margaret McLain who was a Boston University Piano professor. Includes correspondence: 2 WPA letters regarding press release for radio announcers.
  - Program No. 28 Program of Symphonies, 1941; wpa_phono_292; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Unidentified orchestra and conductor. Andante from Clock Symphony; Rondo from Surprise Symphony; Talk by Clifton Fadiman: "What does the WPA accomplish?"; Minuet from Jupiter Symphony.
  - Program No. 29 WPA American Folk Singers of Boston, 1941; wpa_phono_293; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    All songs feature women & men's choruses, a capella. My Lord's gonna move this Wicked Race; Satisfied with Jesus; WPA spot on undernourished children and school lunch program; Some of these Mornings.
  - Program No. 30 Massachusetts WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_294; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Chorale Pathetique; Talk by Charles Taussig, Manufacturer and author: "A business man's analysis of the place of the WPA in American Life"; Scherzo. Pizzicato ostinato from Symphony No. 4, Op. 36.
  - Program No. 31 Southern California Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_295; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Premiere performance of symphony Tableau Russe: Processionale, 1st Movement; Newski Prospect, 2nd Movement; Speech delivered by Lionel Barrymore, composer, on what the WPA has meant to musicians and music lovers; Kremlin; Troika. Recorded live with Barrymore in the studio.
  - Program No. 32 Massachusetts WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_296; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Minuet; Talk by Mrs. Saidie Orr Dunbar, president of the General Federation of Women's Club, on community service WPA project benefits; 1st movement from Henry VIII: Ballet-Divertissement: Introduction - Entrée des Clans.
  - Program No. 33 Southern California WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_297; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Sketches from Fairyland: Queen and the Mirror, 1st movement; Talk by Antoni Van der Voort, composer, on the WPA and his activities; Prince Charming, 3rd movement; Rumpelstiltskin, 4th movement.
  - Program No. 34 Northern California WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_298; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Waltz from Symphony Fantastique; Talk by Dr. John W. Studebaker, U. S. Commissioner of Education, on contributions made by the WPA; Minuet.
  - Program No. 35 WPA American Folk Singers of Boston, 1941; wpa_phono_299; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Mixed chorus, a capella: I got a robe; Religion is a Fortune; WPA spot: Work for Defense; Do, Lord, Remember me; Ain't that Good News.
  - Program No. 36 Northern California WPA Symphony Orchestra, 1941; wpa_phono_300; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Largo from Symphony No. 13 in G Major. Talk by Commander H. M. Cogan, United States Navy and the officer in charge of WPA projects for the U. S. Navy, and the WPA and national defense; Finale from Symphony No. 13 in G Major.
  - Program No. 37 WPA American Folk Singers of Boston, 1941; wpa_phono_301; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00